<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
    id="WatchDog"
    label="WatchDog"
    version="3.1.0"
    provider-name="Software Engineering Research Group (TU Delft)">

    <description url="http://www.testroots.org">
        WatchDog is an Eclipse plugin from TU Delft that unobtrusively monitors how Java applications are developed and tested.
    </description>

    <copyright url="http://www.testroots.org">
        Copyright 2012-2018 Software Engineering Research Group, TU Delft
        http://swerl.tudelft.nl/bin/view/Main/WebHome

        Copyright 2014-2018 The TestRoots Team, http://www.testroots.org

        Copyright 2013 Wouter Willems
        http://wouterwillems.com/
    </copyright>

    <license url="http://www.testroots.org">
        Copyright 2012-2018 Software Engineering Research Group, TU Delft
        http://swerl.tudelft.nl/bin/view/Main/WebHome

        Copyright 2014-2018 Moritz Beller, Tim van der Lippe, Niels Spruit,
	Igor Levaja, Georgios Gousios, Andy Zaidman
        https://www.testroots.org

        Copyright 2013 Wouter Willems
        http://wouterwillems.com/

	
	Privacy Statement / Informed Consent
	WatchDog has been approved by the Human Research Ethics Committee of
	TU Delft, see https://www.testroots.org/assets/papers/ethics_approval.pdf
	
	By registering and installing WatchDog, you agree to our data retention
	and privacy policy:
	- By registering and installing WatchDog, you agree that we store your
	WatchDog data in a data center of TU Delft, The Netherlands, infinitely
	until further notice. The data contains information about how you use
	certain parts of your IDE, mainly in respect to testing, debugging, and
	static analysis. It is timestamped and contains your IP address.
	- You can, but are not obliged to, share personal details such as the
	organization you work for (given permission by your employer) and your
	email address to receive personalized reports. We may report this
	information in a non-traceable way, as long as it does not identify an
	individual (for example, we had users from the Eclipse Foundation).
	- WatchDog follows the principles of least information gathering, early
	anonymization and hashing. We never transfer any plain content of either
	your files or even project or file names.
	- Only the WatchDog team has access to your raw data.
	- You grant us the right to perform scientific research on your data,
	leading to written research papers that might include aggregated user
	data and graphs, and to release fully anonymized (that is, with no
	personally linked identifier such as user id, email, or IP address)
	versions of the submitted WatchDog data.
	- By default, you grant us the right to store your data infinitely until
	revocation.
	- To have your data removed, please simply contact us at
	info@testroots.org, supplying your user id.

	
	License Statement
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
        a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
        &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
        without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
        distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
        permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
        the following conditions:

        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
        included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
        EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
        MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
        NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
        LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
        OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
        WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
    </license>

    <url>
        <update url="http://updatesite.testroots.org/updatesite/"/>
    </url>

    <plugin
        id="nl.tudelft.WatchDog"
        download-size="0"
        install-size="0"
        version="0.0.0"
        unpack="false"/>

</feature>
